# Syed Haseeb

+923463600128

haseebumerzai@gmail.com

I am a Software Engineering graduate with exceptional development qualities. I come up with sound knowledge of Android Applications development. Along with that, I have wide-ranging experience in Web, Windows Apps, Cloud computing, Virtualization and Linux Environment





## **Experience**

10/2022 to Present

#### **Android Developer**

NINESOL Technologies, Islamabad Pakistan

- Product based development
- KOTLIN, MVVM, KOIN

08/2022 to 10/2022

#### **Android Developer**

ITEAS Technologies, Islamabad Pakistan

- Product based development KOTLIN
- Ads Integration (AdMob Facebook)

01/2021 to 03/2021

#### Android Developer

Softech Universe, Rawalpindi Pakistan

- Developing Android Apps JAVA
- Ads Implementation

08/2021 to 10/2021

#### **Asp.Net Developer (Internee)**

PTCL HQ, Islamabad Pakistan

- Delivering different tasks related to Web
- Developing Web sites using ASP.NET
- Networking and Software Installation

10/2021 to Present

#### **System Admin, Invigilator**

AEO, Islamabad Pakistan

- IT support
- Invigilation

10/2019 to Present

# Android Developer Freelancing

Fiverr, Local Projects

## **Highlights**

- KOTLIN
- JAVA
- XMI
- SQLITEROOM
- FIREBASE
- ASP.NET
- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- BASH
- BAT
- DART
- JSON
- C
- C++
- C#
- LINUX

### **Education**

**BSSE (Software Engineering)** 

2018 - 2022

Shaheed Zulfiqar Ali Bhutto Institute of Science and Technology, Islamabad

**Android Development Certification** 

2019

Sina Institute of technology Islamabad

### Languages

English, Urdu, Chinese (Beginner)